Don't do it
I'm giving you a chance
A chance for you to take revenge yourself
This is a video file
Take this with you
Or just have some serious fun with me
Choices come with a price.
- wake up!
- I see
Who will be next?
Oh, more than a friend
Is family more stimulating?
What is the reason for this?
'reason?'
It's fun
Ugh, shit, ugh
Are you sick?
Ugh, uh
Are you surprised?
I'm serious
I said let's play, huh, huh?
Eww
Ugh, ugh!
What the fuck!
Ugh
ah...
You fucking punk, I'm gonna play like this
Do you know who called you?
wake up
Get up, don't hit me
Okay, wake up
Ugh
What the fuck
ah...
Come under me
Fuck you
Come in
Hyung!
turn off
Get out...
Ah, don't do that!
Turn that off
Hyung!
Why? You too
Are you afraid of ending up like this kid?
그거 끄라고, 이 개새끼야!
Hey!
Look, look!
Your friend is getting stabbed
Fighting like that
Why don't you work hard? Hey!
ugh
Eww!
Oh my gosh
Hyung!
brother!
Is this all there is to it?
Ugh
are you okay?
Keep going
oh!
Dude, you should have done this a long time ago, dude.
What the fuck
Eww!
Ugh
Mr. Lee
- Hey!
- Ugh
Ugh
Eww!
Let go, you little shit
ah
Let it go, it's over
You'll regret saving my life.
I am different from you
Different?
Are you different from me?
Am I right?
Breaking news.
Mr. Hyun Mo, the head of a corporate crime syndicate
Arrested today
Mr. Hyun Mo is in the political and financial world
Against celebrities
Illegal sports betting establishments
Operated
Orders for murder, abandonment of bodies, kidnapping, etc.
He was revealed to be the main culprit of a violent incident
It's shocking
This crime committed by Mr. Hyun Mo
Anonymously forwarded to the prosecution
Contained in USB
It was revealed through evidence
A week ago at the Han River
Found as a body
Songgot, the martial arts fighter
At Mr. Hyun Mo's gambling establishment
It was revealed that he was a player belonging to the team
The prosecution is investigating two cases
I think it's related
We are conducting an investigation together
It was revealed
The violent organization created by Mr. Hyun Mo
So-called... disguised as a legitimate company.
Oh, sir.
No, what, now that you've come to this?
Okay, that's it
brother
Me
Already a long time ago
I forgive you, bro
If anyone sees you
I think he's Lee Won-jun's younger brother
I think he's Wonjun Lee's younger brother
It's so good, but it's so noisy
Isn't that right, Jeong Sang-hyeop?
Brother, always
Are you coming empty-handed?
How much is that kid's medical bill?
Until I get rid of all that
Absolutely empty-handed, absolutely
Oppa
If you look at it sometimes, you know that the aftertaste is no joke, right?
Correct answer
Oh, I'm really going alone.
They're so noisy
Wow, I'm your
I'm scared just by turning around
I heard Wonjun's story
brother
I think I get it now
What I really want
What are you talking about?
If you fight
I felt so alive
Things like fighting
People like Bae Seok-chan
I thought you liked it
I enjoyed it too
So I'm going to keep fighting in the future.
Now I'm being dragged by the situation
Not like fighting or anything
I choose myself
I want to fight
What else did I say?
I don't want to be a fighter
Yes, I definitely want to become a fighter.
What, I told you before, what are you talking about again?
Fight me, bro
what?
By working hard
Because I'm going to be a cool player like my brother.
Please fight me then
hey
If you want to be like me
I have to work harder than I am now
You know?
Sharks don't have swim bladders.
They say you swim your whole life
So I don't stop either
I vowed to keep moving
But that determination
What a heavy task
I just found out
Even if Wonjun hyung isn't forgiven
As if I had apologized
Sometimes we do things to get something
Even if you don't achieve 100%
There is something I have to do.
'World Rookie Championship'
I see
5.9 million won...
Ugh
Today's resolution
Even if it comes with another weapon
Today I am constantly
I have to move
I don't fight to live anymore
Because I decided to fight to survive